<resources>
    <string name="app_name">tourism</string>
    <string name="h1">HISTORICAL PLACES</string>
    <string name="h2">FOOD</string>
    <string name="h3">ADVENTURE</string>
    <string name="h4">NIGHT LIFE</string>
    <string name="a1">Red Fort</string>
    <string name="a2">Bhangarh Fort</string>
    <string name="a3">Jalianwala Bagh</string>
    <string name="a4">Taj Mahal</string>
    <string name="a5">Qutb Minar</string>
    <string name="a6">The Red Fort is a historic fort in the city of Delhi in India. It was the main residence of the emperors of the Mughal dynasty for nearly 200 years, until 1856. It is located in the center of Delhi and houses a number of museums.</string>
    <string name="a7">Bhangarh Fort ranks 1st in the list of haunted places in India and is one of the main tourists attractions for people visiting Rajasthan. As Bhangarh Fort is known for its rich history and paranormal incidents, it is one of the most common tourist destinations in India.</string>
    <string name="a8">The Jallianwala Bagh massacre, also known as the Amritsar massacre, took place on 13 April 1919 when troops of the British Indian Army under the command of Colonel Reginald Dyer fired rifles into a crowd of Baishakhi pilgrims, who had gathered in Jallianwala Bagh, Amritsar, Punjab.</string>
    <string name="a9">The Taj Mahal is an ivory-white marble mausoleum on the south bank of the Yamuna river in the Indian city of Agra. It was commissioned in 1632 by the Mughal emperor, Shah Jahan to house the tomb of his favourite wife, Mumtaz Mahal.</string>
    <string name="a10">The Qutub Minar is a minaret that forms a part of the Qutab complex, a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the Mehrauli area of Delhi, Qutub Minar is a 73-metre (239.5 feet) tall tapering tower of five storeys, with a 14.3 metres (47 feet) base diameter, reducing to 2.7 metres (9 feet) at the peak. It contains a spiral staircase of 379 steps.</string>
    <string name="b1">Peshawari</string>
    <string name="b2">Bukhara</string>
    <string name="b3">Indian Accent</string>
    <string name="b4">Gulati</string>
    <string name="b5">Tuscany Garden</string>
    <string name="b6">It delivers North Indian food in Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="b7">The Bukhara at ITC Maurya, New Delhi is a multi-award winning restaurant that brings to life rustic flavours from the delectable cuisine of the North West Frontier.</string>
    <string name="b8">Indian Accent, rated as the no. 1 restaurant in India, showcases an Inventive Indian menu. It is located in a luxury boutique hotel The Manor in New Delhi.</string>
    <string name="b9">The best north Indian Restaurant in New Delhi, India. Serve Vegetarian, Non-Vegetarian, Mughlai Dishes.</string>
    <string name="b10">Tuscany Gardens is a family run restaurant in Candolim, Goa.</string>
    <string name="c1">Bungee Jumping</string>
    <string name="c2">Trekking</string>
    <string name="c3">River Rafting</string>
    <string name="c4">Goa</string>
    <string name="c5">Wing Surfing</string>
    <string name="c6">Rishikesh is the only destination in India where hard-core fans of adventure can have the adrenaline rush of BUNGEE JUMPING.</string>
    <string name="c7">Triund is the crown jewel of dharamshala , situated in the laps of dhauladhar mountains, it has the perfect view of the dhauladhar mountains on one side and kangra valley on the other. Triund is a very popular trekking spot.</string>
    <string name="c8">It\'s one of the major water sports in India, you can enjoy it at different locations like Rishikesh, Manali etc..</string>
    <string name="c10">Feel the adrenaline rush in your veins with the eternal beauty of Kerala’s seaside locations while indulging in windsurfing sport.</string>
    <string name="c9">Goa, one of the top tourist destinations in India, is not just a beauty of sea, sun and sand. But there are much more beyond its tagged beaches and party culture. It is a paradise for water sports lovers too.</string>
    <string name="d1">Club Alibii</string>
    <string name="d2">Kitty Su</string>
    <string name="d3">Club Cubana, Arpora</string>
    <string name="d4">Hard Rock Cafe</string>
    <string name="d5">Xtreme Sports Bar</string>
    <string name="d6">Talk about Mumbai, and the first name that comes to your mind is CLUB ALIBII. This New Year’s Eve they have a ‘Heaven &amp; Hell’ themed party.There will be booze, there will be belly dancers and there will be the who’s who of Bollywood.</string>
    <string name="d7">The KITTY Su at The LALIT, New Delhi. This night club made it to our list because of its DJ who plays the best music from around the globe and to top it all you are served top-end cocktails at the bar, and a full course of lip-smacking cuisines.</string>
    <string name="d8">The club offers beautiful canopied lounges and VIP Jacuzzis under a starlit sky with a kickass chance of bumping into your favourite Page 3 personalities. This left us with just too many butterflies in our stomach.</string>
    <string name="d9">After all, party nights were invented by this brand! Whether you like the music or not, you just have to go to HRC. We visited the HRC in Saket, New Delhi, and the whole club erupted into a rendition of the YMCA.</string>
    <string name="d10">The bar is a haven for sports fanatics. Not your typical club per se, but if you want to blow off the roof while enjoying your favourite sports, this is your place! We certainly love the idea of drooling over Cristiano Ronaldo while partying to some groovy music.</string>
</resources>
